我正在考虑让艾玛吃第一片饼干
You know, I'm thinking about letting Emma have her first cookie.
第一片饼干？她一直都在吃饼干
Her first cookie? She has cookies all the time.
我从没喂她吃过饼干
I've never given her a cookie.
- 你有吗？ - 没有
- Have you?     - No.
顺便一提 我也从没 给她吃过罐子里的糖霜
No. And for the record, I've also never given her frosting from a can.
瑞秋 领养中介需要推荐函
Hey, Rach, the adoption agency needs letters of recommendation...
我们想知道你能不能帮我们写
...and we wondered if you would write one for us?
当然 这是我的荣幸
Of course. I would be honored.
- 谢谢   - 谢谢你
- Thanks.     - Thank you.
我想应该是哪里出错了
I think there's been an oversight.
我们也会想要问你的 只是我们觉得你应该不会有兴趣
Joe, we would have asked you. We thought you wouldn't be interested.
我们觉得你是那种不善表达的人
Yeah, it's just that we don't think of you as really being so much with the words.
很明显地 我们想错了
Clearly, we were wrong.
我有很多你们的好话可以写
I got a lot of nice stuff to say about you guys, okay?
我知道你们多想要孩子
And I know how much you want to have a baby...
我很希望可以帮你们得到孩子
...and I would love to help you get one.
那么就让你来做吧
You know what? Then we want you to do it.
谢谢你们 好吧 我来想想该怎么开头
Thank you. All right. Let me see how I'm gonna start.
"亲爱的领养决定者诸公们"
"Dear Baby Adoption Decider People..."
我们很期待你的信
So excited about your letter.
- 嘿   - 菲比
- Hey.     - Hey, Phoebe.
- 你看起来真美   - 没错
- Wow, don't you look nice.     - Yes, I do.
今天是麦克跟我的一周年纪念日
Today's Mike and my one-year anniversary.
是哪种纪念日？
What's it the anniversary of?
第一次约会 第一次接吻 你们第一次上床？
Your first, uh, date, your first kiss, first time you had sex?
全对
Yeah.
你们一定是要去豪华的地方庆祝
So you must be going somewhere fancy to celebrate.
尼克队的比赛
Uh-huh. Um, a Knicks game.
恩 哈哈 你是不是打扮的有点隆重
Uh, ha, ha... Aren't you a little overdressed?
我从没有过一周年纪念
Hey, I've never had a one-year anniversary before...
所以不管去哪里 我都要穿最华丽的衣服
...so no matter where we go, I'm wearing something fancy...
戴上最棒的珠宝
...and I'm gonna put on my finest jewelry...
还要在公共厕所里面做
...and we're gonna have sex in a public restroom.
你们会那么做吗？
You guys do that?
钱德连在我家厕所 都不愿意做
Chandler won't even have sex in our bathroom.
那是人们便便的地方
That's where people make number two.
- 嘿   - 嘿
- Hey.     - Hey. Hey.
你知道  我有一点时间 如果你想要
So, you know, I have a little time if you want to...
噢 噢
Oh. Oh...
我很想 但我得改这些报告
I'd love to, but I really have to grade these papers.
恩 很好
Oh... Fine. It's fine.
那我就自己去洗澡好了
I'll just shower by myself.
你也给《陶瓷仓》目录B了
Ross, you gave a B to a Pottery Barn catalog.
那上面的论点也挺有趣的 脱掉你的衣服
Well, it had some good ideas. Take off your shirt.
- 讨厌   - 瑞秋 开门 我是你妹妹
- Damn it.     - Rachel, open! It's your sister!
我要跟你谈谈
I have to talk to you.
你好 艾美
Hi, Amy.
- 你不是瑞秋   - 你还是这样敏锐
- You're not Rachel.     - Still sharp as a tack.
查莉 她是瑞秋的妹妹艾美 艾美 她是查莉
Um, Charlie, this is Rachel's sister Amy. Amy, this is Charlie.
- 幸会   - 你好
- Hi. Nice to meet you.     - Hi, hi.
你又是哪位？
And you are?
罗斯？我们是在一个街区长大的？
Ross? I grew up on your block?
去年我们一起吃感恩节大餐？
We had Thanksgiving together last year?
我跟你姐姐生了一个孩子？
I had a baby with your sister?
不 我
No. I...
我昨天是不是 跟你买了一个沙拉三明治？
Did I buy a falafel from you yesterday?
对 你跟我买的
Yes. Yes, you did.
瑞秋 你妹妹艾美来了
Hi, Rachel. Here's your sister Amy.
她觉得我需要做胸肌填充手术
She thinks I need pec implants.
艾美？嗨
Amy? Hi.
- 你记得乔伊吧？ - 当然了
- You remember Joey.     - Yeah. Hey, sure.
- 演《我们的日子》那家伙   - 没错
- The Days of our Lives guy.     - That's right, yeah.
你演得不好
You are not good.
能遇见影迷总是不错
Always nice to meet a fan.
- 你来这里做什么？ - 我有个大消息
- So, now, what are you doing here?     - I have huge news.
- 等等 我去看看宝宝   - 这很重要 艾拉不能等等吗？
- Hold on. Let me check on the baby.     - This is important. Can't Ella wait?
她叫做艾玛
Uh, her name is Emma.
你为什么要改她的名字？艾拉好听多了
Why did you change it? Ella was so much prettier.
我懂什么？我是个卖中东食物的小贩
What do I know? I just sell Middle Eastern food from a cart.
你的英文越来越好了
Hey, your English is getting better.
- 我的天啊   - 我知道
- Oh, my God.     - I know.
她可能是我讨厌的女生里面 最辣的一个
She may be the hottest girl I've ever hated.
- 你在做什么？ - 摩妮卡跟钱德的推荐函
- What you working on?     - Monica and Chandler's recommendation.
我想要看起来聪明一点 但是我不懂得那些艰深的字
I want it to sound smart, but I don't know any big words or anything.
- 你为何不用字库？ - 我说的你没听到吗？
- Why don't you use your thesaurus?     - What did I just say?
你看着
Watch.
先把想要改变的字反白 然后去"工具"
Here, you highlight the word you want to change, uh, go under "tools"...
字库就会产生  给你
...and the thesaurus generates... Gives.
给你很多的选择
Gives a whole list of choices.
你可以选那些听起来聪明的字
You can pick the word that sounds smartest.
老天 太棒了 我变聪明了
My God, that's great. I'm smart.
不 我是
No, no, I'm
"有脑袋的 聪颖的 伶俐的" 我爱死这东西了
"Brainy, bright, clever." I love this thing!
小姐们小心了 乔伊崔比亚尼更完美了
Look out, ladies! Joey Tribbiani's got the whole package!
天啊
God...
太美了
...so beautiful.
我知道 她很美吧？
I know, isn't she?
不 我是说你的床饰
No, I was talking about your bedding.
- 好吧 你的消息是什么？ - 嗯
- All right, what's your news, Amy?     - Oh. Ahem.
这个嘛
Well...
我要结婚了
...I'm getting married.
上帝
Wow! Oh, my God!
- 跟谁？ - 这个人
- To who?     - This guy.
他有间棒呆了的公寓
He has a killer apartment.
- 还有呢？ - 而且在第五大道上
- And?     - And it's on 5th.
电梯一打开就是客厅
And the elevator opens up right into the living room.
- 不 他是怎样的人？ - 他还好啦
- No, what's he like?     - Oh, he's okay.
你记得我的前男友马克吗？
Do you remember my old boyfriend Mark?
- 记得   - 是他的爸爸
- Yeah.     - It's his dad.
- 额 他去哪了  - 老马克
- Huh. Wow, so he's gotta be...     - Old? Yeah.
但他常常出远门 所以不常在家
But he travels a lot, so he's hardly ever there.
亲爱的 这听起来
Sweetie, I gotta tell you, it sounds a little bit like...
像是你喜欢那间公寓比喜欢
...you like the apartment more than you like...
麦伦
Myron.
我跟你说过他很老了
Yeah, I told you he was old.
坐下
Sit down. Sit down.
亲爱的 你知道吗？
Oh, honey, you know...
我也曾经差一点 嫁给我不爱的人
...I once also almost married somebody that I didn't love.
- 你记得贝瑞吧？ - 何止记得
- Do you remember Barry?     - Remember him?
你睡觉以后我们总是打得火热
God, we used to make out all the time after you went to sleep.
有时候你只需要点头就好
Sometimes just nodding is okay.
额 不管怎样 听着
Um... But anyway, listen.
不跟贝瑞结婚是我这辈子 做过最正确的决定
Not marrying Barry was the best decision that I ever, ever made.
艾美 你应该要得到真爱 你的灵魂伴侣一定还在等你
Honey, Amy, you deserve true love. Your soul mate is out there somewhere.
一个跟你年纪相仿 既聪明又有趣
Someone that is your age, that is smart, that is fun...
一个你关心 在乎的人
...and that you care about.
你说得对
You're right.
- 你说得对 我该这么做   - 好
- You're right. I'm gonna do it.     - Okay.
我要跟麦伦结婚 然后继续寻找我的白马王子
I'm gonna marry Myron and keep looking for Mr. Right.
好
Okay.
好 我们继续谈谈好了
Okay, let's keep talking.
借过 周年纪念日
Excuse me. Anniversary.
是的
Um, yeah.
先生 你的玉米片可以拿走吗？这是我的位子
Sir, could you move your nachos? They're in my seat.
今天是我的纪念日
It's my anniversary.
我们到了
Here we are.
- 不敢相信已经整整一年了   - 我知道
- I can't believe it's been a whole year.     - I know.
这是我生命中
This has been the best year...
- 这是我生命中最美好的一年   - 我也是
- This has been the best year of my life!     - Me too!
我从没想过可以这么爱一个人
I never thought I could love someone this much!
我也是这么觉得
I feel the same way!
你是那么慷慨又善良 床上功夫又是一流
You're so generous and kind, and you're amazing in bed!
今天是我们的纪念日
It's our anniversary.
尼克队的球迷 请看计分板上的大萤慕
ANNOUNCER Please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
某人要问个问题
Someone has a special question to ask.
真烂 又低俗又不浪漫
Oh, how lame. It's so tacky and impersonal.
- 真的吗？ - 这是最烂的求婚方法
- Really?     - It's the worst way to propose.
失陪一下
Excuse me.
我的推荐函写好了 拿去
Hey. I finished my recommendation. Here.
我想你们会非常满意
And I think you'll be very, very happy.
这是我除了看色情照片外 花在电脑上最久的时问
It's the longest I ever spent on a computer without looking at porn.
我看不懂
I don't understand.
有些字对你来说太难了吗？
Some of the words a little too sophisticated for you?
这封信根本不通
It doesn't make any sense.
当然 这封信很聪明的 我用了"字库"
Well, of course it does. It's smart. I used a thesaurus.
每个字都用吗？
On every word?
对
Yep.
这一句本来是什么意思？
All right, what was this sentence originally?
"他们是最温暖 心胸最宽阔的好人"
"They are warm, nice people with big hearts."
变成"他们是潮湿 又给人好感的人类
And that became, "They are humid, prepossessing Homo sapiens...
有着全尺寸的大动脉"
...with full-sized aortic pumps."
对 而且我真的这样觉得 老兄
Yeah. Yeah. And hey, I really mean it, dude.
乔伊 我想这封信不能用
All right, Joey, I don't think we can use this.
- 为什么不能？ - 因为你的签名是
- Why not?      - Well, because you signed it
"袋鼠崔比亚尼"
"Baby Kangaroo Tribbiani."
为什么你不能别在乎聪不聪明 当你自己就好？
Why don't you stop worrying about sounding smart and just be yourself?
你不需要字库 只要从这里写出来就好
You don't need a thesaurus. Just write from here.
你的全尺寸大动脉
Your full-sized aortic pump.
- 艾美 嗨   - 我听了你的建议
- Amy. Hi.     - I took your advice.
- 我离开麦伦了   - 做得好
- I left Myron.     - Good for you!
我知道 我就像《永不妥协》的女主角
I know. I'm Erin Brockovich.
对 你是
Yes, you are.
- 我为你感到骄傲   - 谢谢你
- Aw, I'm so proud of you.     - Thank you.
- 哦   - 我能跟你一起住吗？
- Oh.     - So can I stay with you?
但《永不妥协》的女主角 有她自己的房子
But Erin Brockovich had her own house.
看谁回来了
Ah, look who's back
为何你带着行李？她为什么带着行李？
Why do you have bags? Rach, why does she have bags?
我要跟你们住
I'm staying with you guys.
- 什么？ - 我们要成为室友了
- What?     - We're gonna be roomies!
拿吧
Come on.
- 你在这外面睡？ - 对
- You slept out here?     -Yeah.
艾美睡觉的时候一直踢我 还喊着"麦伦 下去"
Amy kept kicking me in her sleep, yelling, "Myron, get off!"
但我们会要她走的吧？我们会要她离开吧？
But, uh, we're getting rid of her, right? Please tell me we're getting rid of her?
- 乔伊 我不能这么做   - 拜托
- Joey, I can't do that.     - Oh, come on.
昨天晚上我吃完披萨的时候 她跟我说
Last night I was finishing off a pizza, and she said
"嘴里一下下 屁股上一辈子"
"A moment on the lips, forever on the hips."
我的屋子里 不需要有人说那种话
I don't need that kind of talk in my house!
乔伊 我知道她很难搞
Joey, look, I know that she's difficult...
但我觉得她在这里很好
...but I think it's really good that she's here.
因为等她走了以后 我们会更快乐吗？
Because we'll appreciate it more when she's gone?
不 当我刚进城来的时候 也跟她差不多嘛
No, it's just... Look, when I first moved to this city, I was a lot like her.
我又骄纵 自我中心 多亏你们大家照顾我
I was spoiled, self-centered. And you guys really took care of me.
对 摩妮卡逼我们的
Yeah. Monica made us.
不管怎样 我都很感谢
Well, whatever. I really appreciate it...
因为如果不是你们
...because I don't think I would be the person that I am today...
我就不会是今天的我
...if it wasn't for you guys.
我想用你们帮助我的方式 来帮助艾美
So I want to help Amy the way you guys helped me.
我知道这要有耐心 但是应该没问题的
And I know it's gonna take patience, but that's okay.
- 早安   - 好
- Good morning.     - Yeah.
艾美 那是我今天要穿的衣服
Amy, that's what I was supposed to wear today.
所以我挂在门上面
That's why I hung it on the door
亲爱的 你撑不起这套衣服的
Oh, sweetie, you can't pull this off.
艾美 我想现在是很好的时机
Amy, you know what? I was thinking that maybe now would be a good time...
我们可以坐下来谈谈你的未来
...for us to sit down and, you know, talk about your future.
我不行 亲爱的 今天我要去修眉毛
Oh, I can't, honey. I'm gonna go get my eyebrows shaped.
我对这个不满意
I am not happy.
额 你确定要吃吗
Uh... Sure you want to eat that?
我身材很有曲线 而且我很喜欢
I'm curvy and I like it!
- 各位   - 菲比
- Hi.    - Hi.
我刚刚过了个最糟的纪念日
I just had the worst anniversary ever.
不见得 告诉她我们去年的事情
I doubt that. Tell her about us last year.
我买了一只五百块的表给钱德 他写了一首饶舌歌给我
Oh, well, I bought Chandler a $500 watch, and he wrote me a rap song.
- 真的吗？ - 真的
- Seriously?     - Word.
我的比这个更糟糕
Well, mine was worse than that.
- 发生什么事情了？ - 我们在看比赛
- Well, what happened?     - We were at the game...
有个家伙在大萤慕上 跟女朋友求婚
...and this guy proposed to his girlfriend on the big screen thing.
- 真的太俗气了  - 我就是这么说的
- Oh, that is so tacky.     - Well, that's what I said.
但结果麦克本来是计划 要在昨晚那样对我求婚的
But it turns out Mike was planning to propose to me that same way last night.
天啊 麦克要求婚了吗？
Oh, my God. Mike was gonna propose?
- 这是大事  - 你想要跟他结婚吗？
- Phoebe, that's huge.     - Do you want to marry him?
想 我很想
Yeah, I really do. Yes.
但是在我这样挖苦他之后
But after I dumped on the way he was gonna propose...
他可能再也不会问我了
...I don't think he's ever gonna ask again.
我在巴贝多说不要 现在又这样
I mean, I said no in Barbados, and now this?
她说得对 如果我是男生
She's right. If I were a guy and...
我刚刚说了"如果我是男生"吗？
Did I just say, "If I were a guy"?
也许不用他来跟你求婚
Maybe you don't need him to propose to you.
你可以跟他求婚
Maybe you could propose to him
我不知道 这样不会太猴急了吗？
Oh, I don't know. I don't know. Isn't that a little desperate?
当时是我向钱德求婚的
I proposed to Chandler.
好吧 请继续说下去
All right, moving on.
我不觉得那样很猴急 我觉得那样很棒
I don't think it was desperate. I think it was amazing.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 你们觉得我该向他求婚吗？ - 我想应该会很不错
- Well, do you think I should propose?     - I think it could be kind of great.
当然 你会爱上这种感觉的 没什么比得上
Absolutely. You'll love the feeling. There's nothing like it.
好吧  那么我该怎么做？
Okay. Okay. So how should I do it?
就在球场的大萤慕上如何？
How about at a game on the big screen?
额 在体育商店怎么样
Huh! How about at a Foot Locker?
怎么了？他显然觉得 那样被求婚很浪漫
What? What, he obviously thinks that's a nice way to be proposed to.
- 再加上他根本不会想到  - 对 有道理
- Plus, he'd never suspect it.     - Yeah, that does make sense.
- 你们两个喜欢这样吗？ - 我觉得不错
- Okay, now, would you two like that?     - Sounds good to me.
但是男生会怎么想呢？
But what would a guy think?
- 外婆在电话上   - 恩
- Uh, Nana's on the phone.    - Wow.
真有趣 她七年前就去世了
That's interesting, since she died seven years ago.
真的吗？
She did?
那她波卡的小公寓给了谁？
Who got her condo in Boca?
你好
Hello?
是我们的保姆
It's our nanny.
你好
Hi.
天啊 我希望你感觉好些 好的 再见
Oh, God, I hope you feel better. Okay. Bye.
是莫莉 她生病了
That's Molly. She's sick.
- 你今天能照顾艾玛吗？ - 我今天的课都是连续的
- Can you watch Emma today?     - I can't. I have back-to-back classes.
莫莉有说她生了什么病吗？因为我的喉咙有点痛痛的
Did Molly say what she had? Because my throat's been hurting.
经痛
Menstrual cramps.
那我的应该不是
I don't think that's what this is.
- 你们哪个人可以帮我照顾艾玛？ - 抱歉 亲爱的
- Can any of you watch Emma?     - No, I'm sorry, sweetie.
我要去工作 然后还要求婚
No, I've got work, and then I'm proposing.
太糟糕了 我要怎么办？
Great. Shoot. What am I gonna do?
我可以帮你
Well, I could do it.
- 其实   - 我可以跟你谈谈吗？
- Well, actually...     - Can I talk to you for a second?
好
Yeah.
我不要她来照顾我们的孩子
Um, I do not want her babysitting our child.
- 为什么不要？ - 她一直叫我们的孩子"艾拉"
- Why not?     - For one thing, she keeps calling her Ella.
- 艾拉也是个不错的名字  - 好 那下一个就叫做艾拉
- Ella's a nice name.     - Fine, we'll call the next one Ella.
- 下一个？ - 好吧
- What, the next one?     - Okay.
我不要她来照顾我们的孩子
I don't want her watching our baby.
我正在帮助她变成一个更好的人
Ross, I am trying to help her become a better person.
这对她来说是个大突破
This is a huge breakthrough for her.
她刚刚才提出 要帮助另一个人的想法
She just offered to do something for another human being.
- 我不知道   - 罗斯 我告诉你
- You know, I don't know     - Ross, I'm telling you...
她为了这个要放弃去修眉毛
...she's giving up getting her eyebrows shaped to do this, all right?
你了解这在我们的世界 是多么重大的一件事情吗？
Do you understand how important that is in our world?
额 听着 我忍不住听
Uh, listen, I couldn't help but overhear, because I was trying to.
让我来吧 我真的很想帮你们
Listen, let me do this. I really want to help you guys out.
再说 瑞秋对我很好
And plus, Rachel's been so wonderful to me.
- 当然可以  - 太好了
- Absolutely.     - Oh, great!
你们要付我多少钱？
So how much does it pay?
推荐函的第二草稿进行得如何？
Hey, Joe. How's the second draft of the letter coming?
很好 我写完了 刚刚才送去中介那里
Great. I'm finished. In fact, I just dropped it off at the agency.
- 你送去了？ - 对
- You dropped it off?     - Yeah.
我们可以看吗？你有印另一份出来吗？
Can we read it? Can you print out another copy?
不能 兄弟
No can do, amigo.
我没有用电脑 我觉得用手写感觉更亲密
No, I didn't use the computer. It felt more personal to handwrite it.
- 你用手写吗？ - 对 而且你们不用担心
- You handwrote it?     - Yeah, and don't worry.
我没有试着展现聪明
I didn't try to sound smart at all.
再见
See you later.
天啊 信会被放进我们的档案里面
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. That letter is gonna go in our file.
我们永远无法领养孩子了
We're never gonna get a kid.
我们会变成那种老夫妻
We're gonna be one of those old couples...
收集兰花或是养很多鸟的那种
...that collects orchids or has a lot of birds.
没关系的 你知道吗？
It's okay. It's okay. You know what?
我来打电话给中介 叫他们把信丢掉
I will just call the agency and tell them to throw out the letter.
好 太好了
Okay, good.
你好 我是钱德宾
Hello, this is Chandler Bing.
是不是有人刚刚送去了 一封手写的谁荐函
Someone just dropped off a handwritten recommendation letter and...
额
Uh-huh.
好
Okay.
谢谢你 再见
Thank you. Goodbye.
我们完蛋了 对不对？
We're screwed, aren't we?
你可以在去鸟店的路上告诉我
You know what? Just tell me on the way to the bird store.
- 他们很喜欢  - 什么？
- They loved it.     - What?
他们觉得要小孩写谁荐函 是很聪明的主意
They thought it was very smart of us to have a child write the recommendation letter.
他们以为乔伊是个小孩？
They thought Joey was a child?
从他的图画上看来 她猜大概是八 九岁
She guessed 8, 9, based on his drawings.
- 嗨  - 你们今天做了什么？
- Hi.    - What'd you guys do today?
艾拉想要出去 所以我们去购物 然后吃了些寿司
Ella wanted to go out, so we went shopping and got some sushi.
- 听起来很好玩   - 不怎么好玩
- That sounds like fun.     - Yeah, not really.
小婴儿好无趣
Babies are dull.
- 我的女孩还好吗？ - 我还不错
- Hey. Hi, how's my girl?     - I'm fine.
因为你让我跟你住 所以我有个礼物要给你
And I got you a present for letting me stay with you.
- 准备好了吗？ - 好了
- Ready?     - Yeah.
嗒 哒
Ta-da!
你把她的耳朵穿洞了？
You pierced her ears?
这样鼻子看起来是不是小一点？
Doesn't it make her nose look smaller?
你把她的耳朵穿洞了？
You pierced her ears?
你怎么不先跟我说就这么做？
How could you do this without telling me?
如果我告诉你的话 就不是个惊喜了 对不对？
If I had told you, then it wouldn't have been a surprise, now would it?
我觉得很可爱
I think she looks cute.
但是我错了
But I am wrong.
天啊  罗斯来了 他一定会气疯的
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Here comes Ross. He's gonna flip out.
为什么 他的三明治车 出了什么事情吗？
Why, did something happen to his falafel cart?
- 大家好   - 罗斯
- Hey, guys.    - Ross!
艾玛 她的帽子怎么戴得这么低？
Hi, Emma. Oh. Why is she wearing her hat so low?
- 这样她根本看不到   - 我不想让她看到
- She can barely see.     - I don't really want her to see.
为什么不要？
Why not?
因为这世界有太多恐怖的画面
Because there are so many terrible sights in this world.
像是战争 或是乔伊冰箱里的那玩意儿 记得吗？
Like war. Or that thing in Joey's refrigerator. Remember?
就是在牛奶盒里面 看起来像肉的那玩意儿？
It was in a milk carton, but it looked like meat?
过来
Come here. Come here.
艾玛在这里 你好
There she is. Hi.
- 怎么了？ - 没事
- What?     - Nothing.
嗨
Hi.
怎么  ？
What...?
- 拜托你告诉我那是夹上去的   - 是真的
- Please tell me those are clip-ons!     - Oh, they're real.
是她干的吗？
Did she do this to her?
我跟你说过不要把艾玛留给她
I told you we shouldn't have left Emma with her!
我知道  你是对的 罗斯
I know. And you were right, Ross.
你真是太不负责任了 我再也不会让你照顾孩子了
Okay? You are so irresponsible! I am never letting you babysit again!
这个孩子需要我
You know what? This kid needs me, okay?
- 她需要一个又酷又有趣的阿姨   - 我就是又酷又有趣的阿姨
- She needs to have a cool, fun aunt.     - I'm a cool, fun aunt.
好吧
Okay.
摩妮卡在整理室内物品的时候 也可以又酷又有趣的
Hey! Monica can be cool and fun at organized indoor projects.
我只是想要让你搞清楚 未来的路要怎么走
All I wanted to do was help you try to figure out what to do with your life.
这就是你报答我的方式吗？
This is how you repay me?
我不需要你的帮忙 我已经知道未来的路要怎么走了
I don't need you to help me. I already know what I'm gonna do with my life.
- 是吗 什么时候知道的？ - 就是今天
- Oh, yeah? Since when?     - Since today.
我要成为一个婴儿造型师
I am going to be a baby stylist.
- 什么？ - 没有这种工作
- What?     - That's not a thing!
那应该要有才对
Well, it should be.
我要帮助小婴儿知道如何配件
I'm gonna help babies learn how to accessorize...
穿什么颜色 怎么穿才瘦
...what colors to wear, what clothes are slimming.
- 小婴儿不在乎自己瘦不瘦   - 所以就该艾美上场了
- Babies don't care if they're slim!     - Enter Amy.
- 艾美  我  我要   - 怎样 你想要怎么样？
- Amy, I... I just... I just wanna...     - What? What are you gonna do?
我不再卖三明治给你了
No more falafel for you!
- 很棒的比赛吧？ - 额
- Great game, huh?     - Uh-huh.
- 你干嘛一直盯着萤慕看？ - 我没有 我只是在祈祷
- Why do you keep looking at the screen?     - I'm not. I'm praying.
拜托 请让尼克队赢得比赛
Please let the Knicks win.
谢谢 索尔
Thank you, Thor.
- 你要去哪里？ - 我要去上厕所
- Where are you going?     - I'm gonna go to the bathroom.
- 我觉得你应该等一下   - 为什么？
- Well, I think you should wait.     - Why?
如果你不忍住 就无法吸收营养
Well, if you don't hold it in, you don't get all the nutrients.
尼克队的支持者 请看计分板上面的大荧幕
ANNOUNCER Please turn your attention to the big screen on the scoreboard.
有人有个特别的问题想问你
Someone has a special question to ask.
麦克汉尼根 你愿意跟我结婚吗？
Mike Hannigan, will you marry me?
大家听好了 女方向男方求婚
Get a load of this. She's proposing to him!
我猜大家都知道 这个家庭会是谁做主了
Guess we know who wears the pants in that family.
这个观念太腐旧了
Well, that's not very enlightened.
嘿
Hey! Hey!
叫什么？去你们的
Boo us? Boo you!
你好 我是乔伊崔比亚尼
Hello? Yeah, this is Joey Tribbiani.
噢 你好
Oh, hi.
我很高兴你们喜欢我写的信
Well, I'm glad you liked my letter.
不 我爸爸妈妈现在不在家
No, my mommy and daddy aren't home right now.
好 再见
Okay, bye-bye.
她人真好
She was nice.
乔伊 去拿艾美的行李 她要搬走了
Joey, get Amy's bags. She is moving out.
唔
Woo-hoo!
- 你要赶我走？ - 你在我女儿的耳朵上打洞
- You're kicking me out?     - You put holes in my baby's ears.
至少现在大家 都知道她是个女孩
At least now people will know she's a girl!
我真是不敢相信 自己竟然试着想要帮助你
I can't believe I ever even tried to help you.
- 你根本是无药可救了   - 你知道吗？
- You are so beyond help!     - You know what?
从我一到这里开始 你一直都很负面
Ever since I got here, you have been nothing but negative.
- 再说一次   - 你说服我放弃
- Excuse me?     - You didn't want me...
跟老家伙结婚 害我不能得到美好的公寓
...to marry the old guy with the great apartment.
接着我想要修饰你女儿的缺陷
Then I tried to help your daughter de-emphasize her flaws...
然后我就变成了大坏人？
...and suddenly I'm the bad guy?
- 乔伊 她的行李呢？ - 她有- 堆东西
- Joey, where are those bags?    - She has a lot of crap!
当我刚到这里来的时候 心里想"太棒了
You know? When I moved in here, I thought, "This will be so great.
我们姐妹又可以 像以前小时候一样
Just us sisters back together again like when we were kids."
除了没那个蠢吉儿以外"
Except without that stupid Jill. Oh.
顺便一提 她变肥了
Who has gotten fat, by the way.
真的吗？
Seriously?
妈说她重了大概15磅
Mom said she gained, like, 15 pounds.
- 屁股还是大腿？ - 屁股和脸
- Hips or thighs?     - Ass and face.
天啊 我以为她在做艾特金斯饮食
Oh, my God! I thought she was on Atkins.
她是 但是碳水化合物不放过她
She was. Carbs found her.
你看 这才是我想要的
See? This is what I wanted.
姐妹们谈谈正经的话题
Two sisters talking about real stuff.
这个我可以给你
Oh, I can give you that.
- 可以吗？ - 对
- You can?    - Yeah.
我一直想要让你变成更好的人
I kept trying to make you a better person, but you're...
但是在你那种人里面 你已经是最好的了
You're already a pretty perfect version of what you are.
谢谢
Thank you.
我得说 艾玛真的很可爱
You gotta admit, Emma does look cute.
- 你刚刚说了"艾玛"？ - 抱歉 应该是"艾拉"
- Did you just say, "Emma"?     - Oh, I'm sorry. Ella.
球场的那个女人 不知道自己在说什么 麦克
That woman didn't know what she was talking about, Mike.
你当然有蛋蛋
Obviously, you have balls.
- 拜托 忘记这回事吧  - 我很乐意
- Please, let's just forget the whole thing.    - I would love it.
- 就当我已经忘记了吧   - 谢谢
- Consider it forgotten.     - Thank you.
但只是要让你知道
But just so you know...
不管你在何时何地决定要求婚 我都会答应的
However and whenever you decide to propose, I promise I'll say yes.
不管是在篮球赛中
Whether, you know, it's at a basketball game...
或是在空中写字
...or in skywriting...
或是像那种可笑电影里的 俗气家伙一样
...or, you know, like some lame guy in a cheesy movie...
在蛋糕里面藏戒指
...who hides it in the cake.
在蛋糕里面 对不对？
It's in the cake, isn't it?
俗气的没蛋蛋先生 还会把戒指藏在哪里？
Where else would lame Mr. No-Balls hide it?
我到底怎么了？怎么一直搞砸这件事？
What's the matter with me? Why do I keep ruining this?
- 对不起 真的很对不起  - 不 这是我的错
- I'm sorry. I'm sorry.     - No, it's my fault.
我一直在找蠢方法向你求婚
I keep trying to propose in these stupid ways...
但我想说的只是我爱你 想要一辈子跟你在一起
...and I just wanna tell you I love you, and I wanna spend my life with you...
- 我现在就要说了  - 我的天啊
- I'm gonna do this now.     - Oh, my God.
- 菲比 我   - 等一下
- Phoebe, I...     - Wait. Oh, wait.
噢 不
Oh, no.
- 可以了吗？ - 额
- Ready?     - Uh-huh.
好了
Okay.
菲比 我爱你
Phoebe, I love you.
世界上没有其他人 可以让我求婚三次
There's no one else in the world I would ask to marry me three times.
但是我想照顾你
But I want to take care of you...
跟你一起生孩子
...have babies with you...
跟你一起变老
...and grow old with you.
菲比布非 你愿意嫁给我吗？
Phoebe Buffay, will you marry me?
愿意
Yes.
- 我爱你   - 我更爱你
- I love you.     - I love you more.
不可能
Not possible.
她要变成没蛋蛋太太了
She's gonna be Mrs. No-Balls!
你的婴儿造型事业进行得如何？
So how's the, uh, baby-styling business going?
不怎么好
Not that great.
好像大家都不想听到 他们的小孩很丑这种话
It's almost as if people don't want to hear that their babies are ugly.
真是令人惊讶
That's shocking.
罗斯在那里 嘿 罗斯
There's Ross. Hey, Ross.
哈罗 罗斯？
Hello, Ross?
他好没礼貌
He's rude.